Oh breakfast!
Gucho and Kimechee Gougeria
Make up
Today was the most fun I've had in Indonesia!
Oh, beautiful!
Good morning
Good morning.
You look beautiful.
Oh, sure.
A beautiful 78.
78?
A view.
Look, look, look, a bicycle.
Huh! Touring! Cycling!
There are so many bikes!
Oh, my gosh! So cute! So cute!
Hey.
Semoga, Sekala, Ikti, Kelaka, Akhyan...
Tomorrow's Strongest Battle
They introduced themselves.
Let's see...
Semoga, Semoanya, Visaska, Pakudaya.
Breakfast
Arrived in my room
Fruit I dropped off
A real child
Come on, let's eat!
Breakfast
Miso soup
Ao-san's miso soup
Bon appétit!
What about watermelon?
Watermelon?
Watermelon and melon?
Melon.
Watermelon.Oh, watermelon
Oh, me too.
Sorry.
Oh, watermelon!
I was just about to.
Yes, it's good.
It's so good.
Oh, mmm.
Oh, it stings.
Yum!
Miso soup is delicious!
It's only miso soup, it's only miso soup
It's just miso soup
I'll eat it as if it's miso soup
Is this curry?
It's not curry, is it?
No, it's not.
Papa, mama, yay! Cute develop sounds good.
You, he's like...
It's like a mango raisin.
what is it?
I think that's what Julia was eating while she was there.
Oh, she mentioned it.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
I'm hungry, so I'm taking a drink from the back.
It's beautiful right in front of you.
You're drinking this?
What's that? Can I grab you now?
Day 16.
Day four.
Since I've been here.
Four days.
This morning was day three.Three mornings.
Three mornings
Fourth day for the big festival
Tomorrow is the last
Tomorrow is the last day
All the tall buildings are here.
That's the only one.
Really?
Yes, really.
I don't understand how you can say it's taller than Japan.
Japan is full of tall buildings.
You don't feel the prestige.
Because it's so tall.
It feels really tall.
Yes, it is.
This is delicious.
It's delicious.
I don't mind if I eat some of the candy I bought as a gift.
I want some.
I tried one today.
What? What?
Oh, you want to try it?
Yeah, sure.
There's a lot of stuff in here.
Look, look, it's normal.
It's normal. - Yeah.
Bye-bye.
I'll do my best today.
Yes, so we've arrived at the venue
It's sunny today
We'll do our best even if it's sunny.
We're going to rehearse now.
Okay?
I just did the bass.
I just curled my hair.I just curled my hair.
It's cool.
What? Why is it cool?
Good luck at rehearsal!
Ladies and gentlemen, please watch my video.
Everyone, please watch my video.
Like, like, like, like.
I like it. I like it.
Cute, cute.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Introduce yourself, please.
Yes, ma'am.
My name is Jillia.
I'm from Japan.
Thank you all for coming to Japan!
Wow! That's perfect!
I memorized it!
I shortened it! I took the liberty!
I jumped for a second, but I can remember!
Yes, I'm a little bit scared!
Merahito!
But I can get it off!
Oh! I've got a bug! On the camera!
Did you see it?
Yes, you're a bad boy!
Semo, semo...
Oh, semo, semo...
Semo...
Semo, semya, isa...
Shika...
Oh, oh!
Akuraya.
Yes, Akucho and Akimekimerai-chan!
Semo, se-mo, se-mo...Semo, let's...
Semo, semo...
Semo, semu...
semo, semanya, isa...
Aku...
Bakudaya!
One more time
Yes, Akucho to Kimekimerai Hitoriichan!
Semo, Semanya, Isa...
Semo, semanya, isa...
Bakudaya!
OK! Let's go!
Rehearsals are over!
It was hard work.
Yes, sir.
Singing was hard!
Because the monitor environment is totally different from Japan.
We couldn't communicate in Japanese, so it was difficult.
I was sweating a lot, wasn't I?
I was sweating so much.
I feel like it's already over.
The rice balls are Japanese
Okoge senbei
I want to try this!
I want to try it
Sarigan-don
But it looks delicious!
Looks so delicious!
There are cookie sandwiches like this.
I love it so much!
I love it!
Let's go!
Ta-da!
Want some?
Want some?Eat?
Eat?
Enaku?
Bon appétit!
Oh, it's so cute!
You're copying Shi-chan, aren't you?
Hmm? No, Celema.
Oh, that's right.
Ceremony mom.
Wait, it's so good!
Yum. Yum.
It's so good. It's so good.
Sax?
Yeah, it's good.
Oh, it's good. It's good. It's good.
What? - What? What? This is delicious. The biscuits are so good.
It's good.
What? It's Enac. It's not too sweet, right?
It's energizing.
Not too sweet, right? It's not too sweet, right?
This is so good. This is so good.
Enakk. This is so good.
Yum, yum, yum.
It's great. It's great.
It's so good. It's so good.
That's close.
So close.
By the way.
Between the bites of rice crackers
And rice
Bring me one.
Thank you.
Japanese crackers
I don't like it
No, no, no...black-marketeering
black-marketeering
I don't want to.
Okay?
Yes.
It's good.
It was delicious.
We have chestnut viewing later today.
I've got chestnuts,
There are chestnuts,
Greetings on the Kyoto stage,
Then I'll do a live performance on the Tokyo stage,
In the evening, I'm going to see Boon's live performance.
I'm super excited.
It's been over 3 years since we met. I met him after 3 years since he wrote a song for me.
He was so kind.
You said it was a parental love.
That's right. He said it was like a parent's heart.
He is very kind.
Well then, I'll do my best after this!
Ah!
I'm going to do my makeup.
Mmm-hmm.
You look so beautiful.
You know, but you're beautiful.
People are already beautiful
More beautiful than anyone
Oh, but it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's good, it's good
Here's my leg, too
And here and there, just the waist is totally fine
But not at all, not at all, not at all
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching.Thank you for watching!
ka, wait a minute, ka, ka, yaaaah!
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Awww!
That was good.
okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
It's Ka-ka.
He killed three of them.
Really?
Yeah.
I'm strong.
Strong.
You can't let them touch you anymore.
Kaa did it.
And Pio, maybe three of them.
Pio?
Pio must've killed at least three of them.
He did.
Good, good. That's a good match, Hiyori.
I already had 3 too.
Aki-chan killed one in a plastic bottle yesterday.
That's great. It's hard to do that.
Cheeks are important.
You too, Aki-chan.
They won't erase it.
To the pilot.
Three.
Color Veil 4 Cheeks No. 11.
Pink Dream.
That's my blush.
Sometimes I put purple on top.
Around here.
This purple, transparency.This purple, transparency.
Yes, transparency.
I'll take it.
Here you go, sir.
Thank you for the food.
Good night.
Mr. Oh, I'm here for a snack.
I hear a customer's voice.
I hear customers' voices.
Pink! Pink!
Thank you for watching!
Oh boy, you're so cute!
Good day to you, please watch again ★
Thank you for watching.
What's up?
Basically, this is my eyeshadow.
And this one.
I'll use this as a metaphor.
This one and this one.
That's right.
HC No. 03 and
Conspicuous.Conspicuous
No. 11 Pink
Amplitude
What's Amplitude?
Amplitude.
It's made of this.
I bought this.
Really? Finally?
It's really cosy.
It's good and it's really cute.
For the show.
They're the exact same color.
I hope you guys like them too.
They're so cute.
Can I recommend it?
It's very cosy.
It's such a good amount.
This much glitter.
It's amazing!
I use it a lot.
It's so pretty.
It's easy to make colors.
There's so many colors.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You can put just one in.
You can just put in a costume.
Just the costume.
And above the eyes.
Right in the middle.
Right where it sticks out the most.
Put it on.
And the boldest.
Put it on.Follow me.
Put it on.
on... on... on... on... on... on...
And be bold.
Hey. Hey.
Sparkle.
Maybe my makeup is simpler than I thought.
Hey, guys.
That's right.
Okay, I'm going for the eyelashes.
Heroine!
Eyelashes are always heroine.
Is it black?
Chelle?
Yes, I do.
That's all.
It was the usual costume make-up.
Lunch
Burger King
Same as yesterday
They eat with their hands.
Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
Oh, it's so crispy, crispy, crispy, crispy, crispy, crispy, crispy, crispy, crispy, crispy, crispy, crispy.
It's so crispy!
That's why they originally came to Japan, Burger King.
I didn't know they were this good.
What? - Burger King is so good!
Enaku!
Yoo-hoo!
I've already had a meal, a delicious meal, and I've finished my makeup.
After this, I'm going to go to Mihuri!
I'm going to go talk bye-bye!
Well, I heard that some Indonesian locals will be there, too!
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm off!I'm off!
Now, I'm going to go to the Kyoto stage, not to Miguri, or whatever it's called, but to the Kyoto stage.
I'm going to Kyoto Stage, no, I'm going to Kyoto Stage to talk to you!
Yay!
Yes!
It's true!
Gradually, Tonton Kamiya
Knock-knock camilla.
What? Kami? Mi?
OK!
Let's go!
Wow! The live show is over!
It was so much fun!
I love, love, love it!
I love, love, love, love!
Everyone sang in chorus!
I've never heard such love
I've never heard it before
So many people sang it!
It was so much fun!
I'm so embarrassed!
Thank you!
Akuchitakan!
It was a lot of fun!
I have an early morning tomorrow.
I'll do my best!
In the meantime, I'm going to take this hair off.
Bye, bye, bye!
Yes!
The concert is over!
I also saw Mr. Karaboon's live performance!
He sang a lot of songs that I know.They sang a lot of songs I knew.
I was so happy! I was so happy to see them singing the theme songs of my favorite anime
I was so happy to hear them sing the theme song of my favorite anime and the theme song of Hiroaca.
It's already dark night! It was like a festival!
It was super, super fun!
I don't know what to say...
Today was the most fun I've had in Indonesia!
It's been dark all day!
It's been a day!
Tomorrow morning is also very early!
I have to leave at 3 in the morning.
I'm going back to the hotel as soon as possible.
I heard they are going to have dinner at the hotel today.
I'm going to have a sweets party with Aki-chan.
I don't know, I'm sleepy and tired.
I'm going to sleep!
So, that's day 5?
26, 27, 28, 29...
Day 4! That's it!
Va-va-va-va-va-va-va!
Dada!
Subscribe to our channel!